question_data = [
    {"category": "Geography",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "A group of islands is called an archipelago.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "The Republic of Malta is the smallest micro-state worldwide.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Vatican City is a country.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Alaska is the largest state in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Toronto is the capital city of the North American country of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Nova Scotia is on the east coast of Canada.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "Rhode Island is actually located on the US mainland, despite its name.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     },
    {"category": "Geography", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
     "question": "There is an island in Japan called Kunoshima, A.K.A. Rabbit Island, "
                 "so named because of it's huge population of rabbits.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
     }
]
